[Referee's Whistle Blows]
Let's have a nice.
clean game. everyone.
Put 'em down.
[Booth] Move the puck.
Wendell. Move it! Move the puck.
- [Player] Up here. Booth. Up here!
- [Player #2] Go!
[Player] Back on "D"!
Pick 'em up on "D." Pick 'em up!
[Brennan] Go. Booth!
Wooh! Go. Booth! Come on!
Kill 'em. Booth!
[Brennan] Whoa! Wow.
What'd he do that for? It's what Booth
does... keeps the other team honest.
He's what you call an "enforcer."
Oh. like law enforcement?
Yeah. okay. Well.
let's go with that.
[Booth] Whoa! What was that?
What about the cross-check?
Ref. are you blind?
Carlson. I'm open.
Pass it! I'm open!
- Pick him off!
- [Number 25] Yes!
- [Whistle Blows]
That was a cheap shot. Carlson.
- [Carlson] Yeah. you guys su...
- [Whistle Blows]
- That's 24 blue.
two minutes for charging.
- [Booth] For what?
- What about
the cross-check back there?
- Get in the box!
Come on. man. It's hockey.
Club hockey. Some of us still
have to go to work in the morning.
[Referee] Enough. Let's go. [Player]
Carlson. calm down. Skate away.
[Carlson] Just
go over in the box.
Get in there and sit down. Let's
go. Yeah. Sit down. crybaby.
- Uh-oh. - [Referee] Let's go.
So. this is punitive. right... to
be sent to this little area here?
Keep your head up next time.
Number 12. Keep your head up!
[Carlson] Yeah. yeah.
I'll be waiting. Come on!
- Hi.
- It's called the penalty box... you know. "sin bin."
Yeah. Booth committed a penalty when he checked
the big guy when he didn't have the puck.
[Number 25] Stay with
him. Carlson. Stay with him!
There's a hit right there.
ref. that you missed. Again!
Booth seems quite anxious to
get out of the disciplinary box.
Yeah. I've never seen
him this agitated before.
Open man! Open man!
[Cheering]
That's not good. right? No.
Go. Booth! Wooh-wooh!
[Referee] All
right. Let's go here.
Ooh. Wendell might get a basket.
[Booth] Elbow. ref! Elbow!
Ooh. is Wendell okay?
That can't be legal.
- It definitely is not.
- [Blows Whistle]
[Player] Come on.
ref. You gotta call that.
Come on. What are
you doin'. Carlson?
Wanna go? Come on. Come on.
Let's go. Come on. Let's go!
- [Players Chattering]
- [Brennan] Whoa.
- [Player] Come on. Booth!
You're a dirty player.
Carlson! [Grunts]
- Come on. ref. Stop the fight.
- Get your hands free!
- Come on. Carlson. You got him!
Hit him!
Don't take shots at
my guys. You got that?
It ends here. okay. Carlson?
- Oh!
- Ooh!
- [Grunts]
- Ends here!
- Booth seems to be winning.
- Well. it's not Booth
I'm worried about.
This guy's out of
control! Come on. ref!
Hey. hey! I'm gonna have to call
a game misconduct on that one.
Get up off the ice. we'll
finish this in the parkin' lot.
If you did your job. I
wouldn't have to do it for you.
Go on. Look at him.
He's hittin' my guys!
- [Player] You all right. buddy?
- [Booth] Son of a bitch.
[Man] All right.
[Woman] Okay. man.
Here we go. Get up.
You all right? [Groans]
Uh. did I score. man? Oh. yeah.
You had a hat trick.
Come on. [Groans]
I do not know how
I feel about this.
- It's very primal.
- I like it...
just a little too much.
[Woman] Come on. team.
[Player] Come on. Let's focus.
[Booth. Groans] So.
you still seein' double?
- Only when I open
more than one eye.
- [Laughs]
- Your hand's busted.
- Yeah. well. you know. Guy left his helmet on.
- Hey. you two all right?
- [Men Chuckling. Chattering]
- Wow.
- What?
Wanna wait outside? Your hand might
be broken. You want me to look at it?
No. it's all right. You
can wait outside. please.
It's a men's locker
room. Bones. [Man] Bye.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Man] There comes
a time in ice fishing...
when it's time for the father to
turn the drilling over to his son.
[Chuckles] Man.
this is a great day.
Hey. you give me beer. let
me run the auger. Yep. [Sighs]
You're 18. Leo. You start
drillin' holes. it's safety first.
You got me? Yeah.
Nothin' I'm saying here applies
only to ice augers. You get me?
Oh. [Chuckles] All right.
Good. You know. that way you
don't fall through the ice and die...
or get a disease
or get pregnant...
Dad. come on. [Clears Throat]
Go ahead. All right.
Attaboy. Keep her perpendicular!
[Drilling Continues]
Once you get in a little bit.
you can speed her
up. let 'er rip. [Chuckles]
All right. Let her rip.
Dad. she... she's bleeding.
- Uh. she's bleeding. Look!
- Pull out. Pull out!
[Motor Stops]
Oh. I hope that's a fish.
You better go wait in the truck.
[Police Radio Chatter] What
do you think there. Bones?
I would surmise that the body went into the
lake before it froze. then the lake froze.
then the body floated up and became
attached to the bottom of the ice.
- I meant. was he murdered?
- Oh. Um. maybe.
Could've been... an
accident or a suicide. except...
- You shouldn't do that.
- It itches. okay?
Yeah. well. except for what?
Trauma to the left maxillary
orbit suggests violence.
- It's kind of gross.
what you're doing.
- Gross?
You got your finger in
some guy's maxillary orbit.
I don't think there's anything
else to be learned here. so...
let's get this Popsicle
back to the lab.
- Hey. look at that. Bones made a joke.
- Well. I can be quite amusing.
- Wait a second.
- Booth. you aren't
wearing any gloves.
Bones. I... Remember that guy I punched
out last month during my hockey game?
Pete Carlson? Yes.
when you broke your hand.
That's him.
I'm a suspect. Here.
Given that Agent Booth is currently
the prime suspect in this murder...
Uh. we don't know it's murder. Huh.
look at that. I'm the prime suspect.
Agent Payton Perotta here
will be working with Dr. Brennan.
I won't work the
case without Booth.
In that case. I invite Agent
Booth's continued participation...
In the background.
as an adviser.
Agent Payton Perotta has
earned bachelor's degrees...
in both forensic
science and criminology.
Well. anything short of a doctorate
is virtually useless at my level.
- [Caroline] How would you
like to proceed. darlin'?
- Well. it's pretty obvious.
We definitely wanna interrogate
the primary suspect. right?
[Quietly] Yep.
Based on decomp.
I'd put time of death...
at about five days
prior to freezing.
Local cops say the lake
froze over three weeks ago.
Aside from some dormant
Anopheles mosquito larvae.
I imagine whatever the
water from the lake tells us.
it'll be through a microscope.
If Booth is a suspect. then I should
be too. This guy scrambled my brains.
Your alibi is that you
were seeing double...
and being taken care
of by your mother.
I'll get on the fluid samples you
took from the lungs and esophagus.
Could be the vic was drowned
somewhere else and then dumped in the lake.
No. Drowning's not the way
Booth would kill someone.
Not... that I actually...
suspect Booth... at all.
Quit staring at me.
In the course of the game. the
victim and I exchanged blows.
Who initiated the
fight? It was hockey.
So it was spontaneous
combustion?
The guy hit two of my players.
The ref... he didn't catch that.
And that made you angry.
Not angry enough. you know.
to chase him down after
the game and kill him.
Where'd you go after the game? Uh.
Bones drove me and Wendell to the hospital.
So no alibi that
night or the next?
Bones and I are just
partners. [Writing. Stops]
Okay. Now you're answering
questions I had no intention of asking.
Is it your contention that. uh. your argument
with the victim was constrained to the ice?
That is my contention. Mmm.
'Cause I have a-a witness...
who stated you told
Carlson. and I quote.
"You get up off that ice...
and we'll settle this
out in the parking lot."
Trash-talking.
- Let me cut to the chase here. Did you kill Pete Carlson?
- No.
- Did you dump his body
in the lake?
- No. I did not. Agent Perotta.
Do you feel that your experience
as the child of an abusive alcoholic...
has made you more
prone to violence?
Excuse me.
What the hell are you doing?
It's part of my job to assist
the interrogating agent.
You know I didn't murder anyone. So what you're
doin' right now is you're just studying me.
That's part of our agreement.
You have a question for me.
you ask me yourself. Don't use her.
All right. Okay. Two questions.
One: Am I picking up some sexual
tension between you and Agent Perotta?
How the hell do I know
what you're pickin' up?
Okay. Uh. two:
Underneath your
affable exterior...
is a deep reservoir of rage.
My question is. do you
always have that under control?
You know if I didn't. you'd be dead
right now instead of just wincing.
- I'm not wincing.
- Well. don't ever bring
my old man up again.
[Door Slams]
Rats! I winced. [Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
So... [Clears Throat]
do you have any more questions?
Thank you.
[Earpiece Hits Table]
[Chuckles] Yeah. Uh...
- You work out much?
- Yeah. I'm pretty consistent.
You look like you take
excellent care of yourself.
Okay. this is useless.
Both patellas are fractured. As
though he'd fallen to his knees?
Yeah. with a
great deal of force.
- During a hockey game?
- No. Not if he wore pads.
I believe that this is
the cause of death.
Penetration of the
lachrymal sac here.
deep into the
inferior orbital fissure.
Yeah. I would've thought
a small-caliber bullet. but...
No sign of bullet
fragments. Yeah.
This is Pete's apartment. He
wasn't the best housekeeper.
Miss Withers. was Mr. Carlson
up-to-date on his rent?
Ah. good question. Great start.
Uh. yes. mostly...
500 bucks short.
He didn't need much.
He was a big kid at heart.
Poor Pete.
What he really loved was hockey.
I wouldn't be surprised if that's why
he joined the volunteer fire department.
I even got him this necklace.
- Some crossed hockey sticks.
- [Camera Shutter Clicks]
- You attended his games?
- Oh. all of 'em. Yeah.
You were a couple?
It looks like someone went through all of his
belongings and then left them on the floor.
Oh. it always looked like that.
The car outside with
the flat tires... is that his?
Yeah. Somebody slashed the
tires just before he disappeared.
Why didn't you
report him missing?
I thought. maybe. mmm...
I thought he was staying
with someone else.
There's a lot of bills here:
"Final Notice." "Past Due."
Looks like he couldn't
afford to feed his fish either.
"Albie... Thursday. 11:00 p.m."
- Do you know who Albie is?
- I don't know.
- This is blood.
- It's a hockey jersey. Bones.
Hockey players bleed sometimes
when they play the game.
Miss Withers. how bad
were his financial problems?
Well. a couple days
before Pete disappeared.
he asked me for $2.000.
Did he say what for?
He liked me. you know?
He was one of these guys...
He... He didn't say much.
but he could be real sweet.
And a man borrows
money from a woman...
It means there's a
bond of trust. right?
I don't understand
your reasoning. I do.
It's definitely a... bond of
trust. You're absolutely right.
We're terribly
sorry for your loss.
Is that our victim? Yes.
The last of the tissue samples.
Wendell can clean the skeleton
now. and you can do your thing.
Oh. you still think the cause of death
was a projectile through the left eye?
Yes. but since we found
no bullet. nor any indication...
of gunpowder residue in the wound. we're
stumped as to what kind of projectile.
The alveolus around the incisor is
cracked. the socket caked with blood.
- This is a recent loss.
- Well. he was a hockey player.
- So basically we're talking
about gladiators.
- And I love it.
Perhaps the sight
of males battling...
stimulates the
part of your brain...
which has so far failed
to find a suitable mate.
And thank God you're here.
The water I found in the victim's
esophagus... not from the lake.
Lake water is
microorganism infested.
Water in his throat...
Deionized brine water.
He was killed. then dumped in
the ocean. then dumped in the lake?
Deionized brine water freezes
clear. Contains an anti-freezing agent...
- which I know sounds
counterintuitive...
- Ice rinks!
[Chuckles]
Kind of jumped my punch
line there. Dr. B. But yes.
We should see what rinks are closest
to the lake. It's the one Booth played at.
I find it interesting that the evidence
keeps pointing toward Booth.
- Pete Carlson was murdered?
- Pete... he's indestructible.
Not so indestructible. This guy
took him down a few notches.
Made him stay down too. It was the heat
of the game. Your guy crossed the line.
Yeah. he was our enforcer.
Took the job real serious.
Well. whoever got Pete must've got
a drop on him. Pete wouldn't go easy.
You mind my asking why
nobody reported him missing?
The night after you flattened Pete.
we go up against the state police.
Pete gets into a beef with a
big state police left-winger.
'Cause you handed him his ass on a platter.
Pete maybe had somethin' to prove that night.
- You got a name?
- Hey. Alex!
Yo! Come here.
The Fuzz player that Pete got into it with
his last game... you remember his name?
- Yeah. Lou Herrin. Number Five.
- So Pete took Herrin down
with a real cheap shot.
He got tossed out
the rest of the season.
Any chance that Pete and this guy
Herrin continued their fight off the ice?
People threaten. Yeah.
but nobody carries through.
Yeah. Keep it on the ice. right?
If I were you. I would talk
to Chloe. Who's Chloe?
- [Player] Chloe Bratton.
- [Player #2] Chloe's a puck bunny.
Her and Pete put in some quality
mattress time before he dumped her.
Well. a mattress really isn't. uh.
Chloe's style. but. uh... No offense.
None taken. Favor
backseats myself.
[Chuckles]
I can't believe Pete's gone.
How long ago did you
two break up? Break up?
- We didn't break up.
- His teammates
think you did.
No. We had this
on-again. off-again thing.
It was casual. No biggie. So-So you didn't
mind that he slept with different women?
I wouldn't have minded if he
did. but I happen to know he didn't.
Oh. I happen to
know that he did.
- [Quietly] Right.
- Who?
Oh. it doesn't matter. does it. given
that your relationship was so. um. casual?
- You slashed his tires.
didn't you?
- Agent Booth.
- No.
- We can prove you did it.
Chloe. So here's the deal.
You tell us the truth from now
on. and we won't charge you...
with vandalism and
obstruction of justice. okay?
Let's try this again. You
slashed... Agent Booth.
[Quietly] Yes. Of course.
Let's try this again. You
slashed his tires. didn't you?
Yes.
I mean. he was sleeping
with someone else.
I got passions that
take over sometimes.
You know how it is when the guy you give
yourself to just goes off with someone else.
- Who's. um. Albie?
- Albie?
Albie runs this poker game in back
of a Chinese food joint off I Street.
Probably why Pete was broke all the time.
So who'd you say Pete was sleeping with?
I think we've got enough
information for today. Miss Bratton.
- Thank you very much
for your cooperation.
- [Booth] Thanks.
[Saroyan] Any luck with
the murder weapon? Yes.
We are certain it
is not a screwdriver.
Well. the blood on the
victim's jersey was all his own.
The rib cage has
been bruised. It has?
Yes. See this vague
pattern of bone bruising?
[Wendell] Yeah. it extends
from the right clavicle...
through anterior ribs
four through eight.
He was... struck repeatedly.
What. by a hockey stick?
During the game maybe?
Not during. The. um. padding
would prevent that kind of bruising.
I'll take a closer look. Uh. I
can't believe I missed that.
[Mouths Word]
No. I can't believe
you missed that either.
I was signaling you to
encourage Wendell...
by saying. "Anyone
could've missed that." but...
You should've said so.
Booth says I stink at
nonverbal communication.
[Whispering] She
said in the back.
Okay. Just don't be pullin' your
gun until you go through the kitchen.
or mama-san there is
gonna hit the panic button.
Got it? Okay. just go.
[Murmurs]
So you're ready to risk a gunfight
with your weapon in the wrong hand.
I don't have a wrong
hand. I'm curious.
When you shoot with your left hand. does
it feel like somebody else is shooting?
Easy!
Ah.
What do we do now? Okay. F.B.I.
Okay. I'd reach for my badge
right now. but. you know. I...
- Drop your weapons. please.
- Please. The F.B.I. does not say "please."
Okay. look. I really don't
care about the illegal gambling.
I just wanna talk to
a guy named Albie...
about a guy named Pete Carlson.
[Guns Uncock]
I'm Albie.
First rule. don't kill the
people who owe you money.
All you get then is
trouble and no money.
How much money
did Carlson owe you?
Okay. So. you got your operation
shut down and moved out?
Because I could have my guys
here in about. what. three minutes...
to mop that back room up.
Pete Carlson was not a
bad player most of the time.
but. you know. every
once in a while...
He got brave and
lost everything.
- Gamble a bit yourself. do you?
- I'm reformed.
Tell me. when was the last
time Carlson got. um. "brave"?
Last month. But he paid up
in full a couple of days later.
Cash?
A little garish.
don't you think?
- I don't know where Pete got it.
but it covered his debt.
- I'm gonna have to take this.
If I didn't intend to give it to
you. you'd never have seen it.
Okay. you gave me the time I needed to
move my operation. I gave you evidence.
I call us square.
You decide to get back into
the game. you look me up.
Right. Yeah.
Well. we gonna call this in?
Oh. no point. Like the
woman said. she's moved on.
Hodgins confirmed that the traces of
rink water in the victim's esophagus...
[Murmurs] came from this rink.
Well. how did rink ice get
into his throat? He was beaten.
then a sharp instrument
was thrust into his eye.
There should be... blood stains.
You're going to scan the
ice with one little wand?
I'll call an F.B.I. forensics team.
We'll have the whole place searched.
No need. All you need
is black light. right?
Yes. Right? I got
a great idea. Just...
Whoa. Stay here. It's
very slippery. Don't move.
[Booth] Ready? How's
that. huh? [Brennan] Nice.
[Perotta] Wow. Gonna work?
Well. I see some.
uh. flecks of blood.
No. we're looking for something
bigger than these small specks and spots.
If the victim was stabbed in the eye. we're
looking for a pretty significant puddle.
Two guys get into a beef. then
they put their street clothes on...
and then come back here
on the ice and duke it out?
Booth. Yeah.
[Booth] Whoa.
[Perotta] Oh. my God.
This is going to turn out to be
where Pete Carlson was murdered.
[Device Beeps] This is all
the ice from the crime scene.
including the scrapings
from the Zamboni.
We should be able to get enough D.N.A. out
of this to confirm the blood is Carlson's.
Whoa. Human tooth.
It's hockey. That Zamboni
probably had a hundred teeth in there.
Looks like we found
where the tooth fairy winters.
[Sighs] Did you find a
match yet? Just started.
Shows it's definitely
the victim's blood.
I still haven't found
the murder weapon.
I still haven't identified the nylon
polymer I found on the victim's shirt.
So I've looked at. like.
a thousand photos...
of those blood patterns at the
rink and tons from the apartment.
- Why? What are you lookin' for?
- Here's a blood pattern
at the rink.
The body was
dragged in that direction.
Yeah. the body was dragged that
way. but what are those drops over there?
What drops? Those
drops right there.
They parallel the dragging
body. And they aren't smeared.
These parallel drops
aren't from the victim.
They're from whoever
dragged him across the ice.
Well. that means we have to
check for more than just Pete's D.N.A.
Too bad we can't
question the fish.
- What killed those fish?
- Not eating for three weeks?
If that happened. they
would eat each other.
Oh...
Grab your coat. We're
goin' on a field trip.
And tell Cam to check the rink samples to find
out if there was a second source of D.N.A.
I-I'm not really
a big fan of this...
"barking out orders" stuff.
[Cell Phone Beeping]
[Sweets] Agent
Booth? [Booth] Mmm?
It's come to the attention
of the deputy director...
that you are a viable
suspect in a murder case.
Right. Okay. and he wants you
to make sure that I'm not viable.
That's correct. Come on. Sweets.
You know I didn't kill anyone.
So. you know. put
that in shrink talk.
and... write out your
little form and send it in.
Mmm. Mm-hmm. Yes.
of course. But to do that.
- I need to ask you
some questions.
- [Sighs]
All right. [Clears
Throat] Shoot.
I saw you in that game. You
beat another man to the ice.
It's hockey. I was
protecting my teammate.
- You broke your hand
on his helmet.
- It's hockey. okay?
- You never played. did you?
- Oh. I've run track
and cross-country...
and did some wrestling
and ch... [Laughing]
Chess. No.
- Checkers?
- Didn't say that.
You know what? Then you know
nothing. It's about teams. okay?
And teamwork? Obviously you don't
know anything about that. Dr. Sweets.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. mm-hmm.
You joined the army.
You became a sniper.
- Mm-hmm.
- You joined the F.B.I.
Do you see the. uh... the
binding element in those choices?
It's violence.
Or the love of uniforms.
You ever think that?
Agent Booth... [Sighs]
I believe that you are
ready to confront the fact...
that the violence you may
have suffered in childhood...
You know what? has
followed you into adulthood.
Fill out the form.
[Knocking]
- Not now.
- Hiya. Sweets.
Uh. if you're about
finished here. Booth...
In accordance with the
warrant you made me get.
Pete Carlson's phone
records are here.
Miss Julian. actually. I'm the one
that decides when we're done here.
Of course you are.
chéri. No offense intended.
I'll be deliverin' the phone
records to Agent Perotta.
- I thought I'd do that
in your office.
- Thanks. chérie.
We're done.
Well. ye... We are done. but
that was just a coincidence.
Sweets. I've killed. but
I've never murdered before.
Look up the difference in your
little black book there. okay?
[Door Closes]
This is legal.
right? Absolutely.
[Wendell] Okay.
[Door Closes]
None of 'em look nibbled on.
Oh. man. they should've
gone at each other...
like a Peruvian soccer
team stranded in the Andes.
Then they all died
at the same time.
- I don't see
what this is gonna tell us.
- How they died?
- No. no. I... I mean. about the case.
- Ooh. hoo. hoo.
If Brennan were here.
she'd smack your face.
Her philosophy is. we find
out the facts about everything.
then see how it fits together.
Photo opportunity. Oh.
Pete made eight calls right after
the game. but the same number.
- Lou Herrin... who's that?
- Oh. sergeant
in the state cops.
He exchanged blows with
the victim the night that he died.
Make it official.
Question the cop.
Let's get some leverage on the guy
first... put him at the murder scene.
- Get a warrant
to test his D.N.A.
- Here we go.
Get a warrant for this. Miss
Julian. Get a warrant for that.
You need grounds for a warrant. chérie.
Don't they teach that at Quantico anymore?
What grounds have
you got for that warrant?
None. Nothin'.
You're just wishin'.
I know how to get some
blood out of this Herrin.
- Legally?
- Yeah. Of course. legally.
- How?
- Well. there's a big game
tonight. right?
And sometimes. durin' a game.
people bleed. huh?
- [Sighs] I don't like it.
- Then you don't have to show up.
[Sawing Continues]
[Exhales]
Whoa. What are you doin'. man?
What does it look like I'm doin'?
Think that's a good idea? You got
another couple of weeks on that cast.
Well. considering I can't play with
a cast on. yeah. it's a great idea.
You clear about the plan?
If somebody bleeds.
I collect a sample.
put it in a bag and pass
it off to Dr. Brennan.
Lou Herrin. Number Five...
He's our prime suspect.
And I gotta make him
bleed. [Cast Cracking]
[Players Chattering]
- You've worked with Booth
for a while now. right?
- Mm-hmm.
Is he the kind of guy that.
uh. you know. I mean...
Is he... flirty? Flirty?
Would you say he twinkles
his eyes at all women?
Twinkly eyes actually result
when the pupils dilate very wide.
which is an unconscious result of
intense interest or sexual attraction.
So. no. he doesn't
twinkle at everyone.
No. All right.
[Whistle Blows]
- Is that the guy?
- That's him. Lou Herrin. Number Five.
Wow. Do you think he
even knows how to bleed?
Just keep your head up.
all right? [Whistle Blows]
Ow!
[Player] Come on. You
should've called that.
[Player #2] Pass
it up. That's a trip!
[Both Grunting]
[Booth] Keep your
head up. Herrin.
[Brennan Shudders]
Man. what's your problem?
I got a little chip. all right? It's Flyer
hockey. pal. This guy's hard to get mad.
Man. he's maybe the only
one who hasn't shed a drop.
[Players Chattering]
Stay outta my crease.
Keep your head up. huh?
[Grunts]
- Take a warning. pal.
- [Strains]
I think I'm finally
gettin' to this guy.
Yeah. Hope you survive it!
[Both Grunting]
Ah! [Groans]
- Taking a little break?
- [Sighs]
- Luc Robitaille?
- Seeley Booth.
- Right.
- Let's go. Let's play.
Right.
You're the greatest
left-winger of all time.
And you're the best player on
your team. for what that's worth.
All right. let's go. Come on.
Let's play. [Stick Raps On Ice]
[Robitaille] There we go.
Come on. Show me something.
Head up. Attaboy.
Come on. Move. move.
move. move. move! Let's go.
Whoa. Wait a second. I can't play
hockey with you. I gotta solve a murder.
You know. Booth.
it's not about the blood.
[Booth] It's the
best forensic clue.
- Forget the blood.
- Then what?
You know what makes a team.
Look at the team. It's about
what brings a team together.
The team. Look at the team.
All right. let's go. One-on-one.
[Stick Raps On Ice]
Let's see what you
got. Come on. B.
Whoa! Aw. geez. I thought I
could get by you there again.
- You'll never get by me.
- Right.
Now listen. Booth. You're
not your father. okay?
You protect the ones you care
about on the ice and off the ice.
That's who you are.
You're not your father. Booth.
[Echoing] You're not your
father. [Brennan] Booth?
You're not your father. Booth?
Booth?
Bones. what are
you doin' on the ice?
Well. I get nervous when
you fall down and don't get up.
Come on. Here. [Sighs]
Up you go. buddy.
Come on. Come on.
Don't worry. I got the blood.
- Good work. Bones.
- But I'm Bones.
[Whirring. Stops]
Ugh. Smells like fish in here.
Yeah. It's the
victim's goldfish.
They died of ammonia poisoning.
How did that
happen? I don't know.
Maybe the victim washed his
aquarium with window cleaner?
I don't know. How are
things with you and Roxy?
Oh. good. Good.
Taking it slow. you know.
Letting things unfold in a...
Are you seeing anybody? I. um...
Actually... [Chuckles]
went out on a date last night.
Oh. I'm glad to hear that.
Any little twinge there?
Definitely a little
twinge. yeah. but...
despite the twinge. I'm glad
you're back in the saddle.
Oh. I'm not back in the saddle
exactly. It was just a first date.
Barely got out of
the barn. [Laughs]
You saw the victim's
apartment. right?
Yes. Yeah. yeah.
It was a pigsty.
I don't think that guy
cleaned anything...
Not with ammonia.
not with anything.
I came as soon as I heard
Booth had a brain injury.
What... What part of your head
hurts? The part above my shoulders.
The doctor said he has a
concussion. He shouldn't fall asleep.
Otherwise. not serious.
- Tell him about
the hallucination.
- You hallucinated?
Luc Robitaille gave me advice.
- You got advice
on a murder case from...
- What did he say?
He said. "Don't worry about
the... the player's blood."
Oh. That's very interesting.
Lucky Luc told me to
look in a different direction.
[Sweets] That's interesting.
Stop saying that. Just... Stop.
Preliminary D.N.A. tests show that
the blood mixed in with the victim's...
did not belong to Lou Herrin.
- Lucky Luc was right.
- No. all that means...
is that you got your brains
scrambled for nothing.
No. Lucky Luc is never wrong.
This hallucination could be. uh.
Booth's subconscious speaking to him...
through the voice and image
of someone that he idolizes.
Like a modern version
of a vision quest?
Oh. you know what?
Hallucination or not... [Groans]
Lucky Luc... he told me
somethin' about myself that...
- He told me something.
- I'd be very interested
in knowing what he said.
Lucky for me. you're
never gonna find out...
because Bones is
gonna drive me home...
What? and get me soup. [Groans]
[Hodgins] There's gotta be some reason
these fish died of ammonia poisoning.
Last time I did this. I ended up
in juvie hall over the weekend.
What? What? Uh. nothing.
Whoa. Wow.
Oh. wow.
Buried treasure.
What do we do now?
Find out why the hell he was
hiding jewelry in a fish tank.
Have any of you ever heard of
something called "chain of evidence"?
Miss Julian...
Why didn't you go with these
two idiots to the victim's home?
- Please don't call
my people idiots.
- We're not idiots.
- I feel like an idiot.
- You don't speak right now... either of you.
[Saroyan] It's a crime scene.
My people are very often at
crime scenes. It's what we do.
No. it's not. You've got it in your
heads that you're crime-scene types.
This is Booth's fault for indulging your
fantasies. You are not crime-scene types.
- You are lab rats.
- No chain of evidence
was broken.
When Dr. Hodgins and Mr. Bray found
the items. they immediately called me.
I called Booth. and when his head hurt too
much to talk to me. I called Agent Perotta.
- Miss Julian.
- What?
A photograph of dead
fish led them to this.
I think that kind of
brilliance is worth it.
You've been taken hostage
by the squints. Agent Perotta.
Turns out these items were
reported destroyed in a fire.
The victim was a fireman.
The F.B.I. could check to see
if the Firedawgs put out that fire.
Stole from the fire.
cleaned off with ammonia.
Hidden in the
aquarium. killed the fish.
Okay. Now you are
straying out of your territory.
No. They got it right.
The bracelet Agents Booth and Perotta
recovered from the victim's loan shark...
was reported destroyed
by that same fire.
- Hmm. My people were right.
- [Together] Your people?
- [Together] We're Booth's people.
- Hmm.
[Groans]
[Sighing]
They're on the Firedawgs.
but they also played on
the same high school team.
[Quietly] What brings them
together. eh? [Door Opens]
I'm back.
[Door Closes] [Continues Quietly]
Hey. what brings them together?
What brings the team together?
So I got the soup from the
place. And yes. I told "Mama"...
that it was for you
especially. [Clears Throat]
[Quietly] It's all about
the team there. It's all...
What are you doing? It's
all about the team there.
Bones. it's all about
the team there. They...
These four guys... they all played
hockey together in high school.
and now they all play
together as a team.
They're all firemen? Yeah. they
all worked the jewelry store fire.
One of these three
guys is the murderer.
According to
Mr. Lucky? [Pen Clatters]
Ow. It's Luc. okay? It is...
I-It's not "Mr. Lucky."
It is Luc Robitaille.
Left wing. Great shot.
Luc Robitaille. He's one of
the best left-wingers of all time.
- What is this?
- It's a lace puller. Why?
I think it might be
the murder weapon.
We want to discuss
the jewelry store fire.
I want a lawyer. What for. Alex?
- We didn't do anything wrong. None of us did.
- What about Pete?
He break some kind of fireman
code. somethin' like that?
Yeah. somethin' like that.
I've got nothin' to say about
any of this. I want a lawyer.
We know Carlson was
beaten with a hockey stick.
after which. a lace puller entered his
brain through his eye and killed him.
What about your dream. Ed?
You were gonna
play for the NHL. right?
"Local Player Scouted by
the NHL." Look at that one.
Oh. this one's good too:
"Fralic's Hat Trick Wins Game."
I got injured.
This injury would end any chance
of a career in professional hockey.
- What does that have to do
with anything?
- Look. I got hurt.
Now I sell siding and play hockey on the
weekends. Why rub his face in the past?
Who ruined you?
Pete Carlson.
- It was Pete.
- You all knew about
the stolen jewelry?
Question is. how many of you
were there the night he was killed?
None of us. Nobody here
had anything to do with that.
We have the hockey stick.
the murder weapon and D.N.A.
It's only a matter of time.
Yeah.
- What?
- It was me.
I asked to meet Pete on
the ice after everybody left.
I told him to give
back the stolen jewelry.
And he said to me... He...
He said to me that
I was a... a coward.
that I didn't do
anything to him...
back in the day when
he wrecked my life...
and I wouldn't do
anything to him now.
Well. he was wrong.
- I'm not positive
this is a good idea.
- [Booth Chuckles]
[Yelps] Oh. I gotcha! I
gotcha. Stay up here.
[Laughing] Okay. It's all
right. Here we go. One more.
You know what? I
gotta stay up all night.
So who better to keep me
company than you? [Laughing]
You and me skating is saving
you from slipping into a coma? Oh...
Ah-Ah! Easy. Bones.
Now I'm gonna go down.
I have a lot of
natural athletic ability.
Oh. yeah. Natural. I can...
I can see that. [Chuckles]
Real smooth and
natural. That's it.
Relax. Oh. [Yelps]
That Agent Perotta... she
really enjoyed working with us.
Yeah. But. um.
you're the only F.B.I.
agent I want to work with.
- Will you tell me what the... Lucky Luciano told you?
- He's not an opera singer.
Why do you always say that wrong?
You do it on purpose. don't you?
I would like to
know what he said.
He said that I'm not
like... my old man.
He said I'm made
of better stuff.
Well. I don't know your
"old man"... your father...
But...
I think you're made
of very. very good stuff.
Hey. know what? Forget
about Agent Perotta. all right?
Nothing's gonna change
between me and you.
Well. entropy is a natural force that pulls
everything apart at a subatomic level.
Everything changes.
Don't! Not everything. Bones.
[Yelps] [Laughing]
Not everything.
You're gonna make me fall.
I'm never gonna make you fall.
I'm always here. You kiddin'
me? This is kinda fun actually.
Yes. see. I can... Watch.
here comes the big spin. Uh-oh.
[Brennan Laughs] Whoa!
[Chattering] Go easy.
What's that mean?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm